[
  {
    "name": "riddle_0",
    "question": "Please come closer, you must understand, I simply cannot see. I've lived long, far from your school, with my humongous family.",
    "answer": "aragog"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_1",
    "question": "In old English, my name means bumblebee, and the Order of Merlin First Class was given to me.",
    "answer": "dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_2",
    "question": "Our victory in the 1994 Quidditch World Cup drew cheers from some, but certainly not from Viktor Krum.",
    "answer": "ireland"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_3",
    "question": "Going to the kitchens? Well don't forget! Tickle me, or access you will not get.",
    "answer": "pear"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_4",
    "question":
      "Towards the Slytherin students, people say I showed bias, I am the son of Eileen and Tobias",
    "answer": "snape"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_5",
    "question": "My code name on 'Potter Watch' was Romulus, surely you can guess who I am, without too much fuss?",
    "answer": "lupin"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_6",
    "question": "Enter Hogwarts and 142 of these you can see, just be sure to tread carefully.",
    "answer": "stairs"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_7",
    "question": "James to some, to others I'm the father of Harry, but as a Marauder, this was the name given to me.",
    "answer": "prongs"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_8",
    "question": "I roam the woods of Hogwarts school and my coat is a lovely white, but don't you dare try to drink my blood, or you'll be cursed for life. Who am I?",
    "answer": "centaur"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_9",
    "question": "Harry used Polyjuice potion and his body became fuller, but add one of Harry's hairs to the potion, and it will become this colour.",
    "answer": "gold"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_10",
    "question":
      "Buckbeak was a hipogriff, considered by Hagrid to be tame, but after the death of Sirius, he was given what name?",
    "answer": "witherwings"
  },
  {
    "name": "riddle_11",
    "question": "Cauldron Cakes, Chocolate Frogs...they both hit the spot, but Harry's favourite treat, is a tart made of what?",
    "answer": "treacle"
  },
    {
    "name": "riddle_12",
    "question": "Red of hair, and loyal to the end, but what is the middle name of Harry's best friend?",
    "answer": "bilius"
  }
]